

AR/VR/GAME DEVELOPER · UNITY

300 Cattlemans Cir, McDonough Ga 30252

□ (770) 316-7079 | 🗷 travis.gunnyon@gmail.com | 🔏 travis-gunnyon.github.io/DevPortfolio/ | 🛅 travis-gunnyon

Summary

Over the years my role as a Unity Developer morphed as technology has progressed. I started my career as a game developer for mobile devices until the emergence of new technologies in the augmented and virtual reality space evolved. I have been fortunate enough to have had the ability to handle and experiment on a wide range of cutting edge devices and absolutely love to discover new ways to bring media and experience to life for clients in ways they never imagined. Developing in Unity in C-Sharp over the years I have become fairly proficient at accomplishing tasks asked of me while continuing to learn new practices features of .Net Framework.

Work Experience

Collabera

Basking Ridge, New Jersey(REMOTE)

AR Developer/Consultant

August 2021 - Current

- Contracted with Ally Financial to assist in helping them explore AR use cases and create proof of concepts in connection with the Ally Tech Labs team for both internal and customer facing applications
- · Create an internal app to display various AR concepts to aid in exciting leadership during a visual presentation
- · Assisting Collabera in the interview process concerning Unity developers for other projects/clients

Freelance Unity Developer

McDonough, Georgia

AR/VR/GAME UNITY DEVELOPER

May 2021 - Current

- Contracted by Delta thru Trick 3D to assist in taking parts of a previous project("AR/VR Flight Attendant Training Program") and integrating into their native demo app utilizing UaaL, Unity as a library
- Contracted by Trick 3D to update a VR tour experience for Atwell Suites to be ran on on Pico headset, updating their micro-site and making changes to the web hosted virtual tour in Pano2VR

NexTech AR Solutions Atlanta, Georgia

UNITY DEVELOPER

Oct. 2020 - May. 2021

- Unity Developer Continued development of the AiR Show augmented reality application on both IOS and Android. Expanding features while maintaining a quality product on an Agile development team. Exploring experimental requests and documenting results in order to push the limits of current technology.
- Updating and maintaining Jira tickets while documenting information in Confluence while working with other teams members and keeping line of communication open while working remote.
- "AiR Show" project and team was acquired by NexTech AR from TRICK 3D

TRICK 3D Atlanta, Georgia

AR/VR/GAME DEVELOPER

Sept. 2012 - Oct. 2020

- Unity Game Developer Developing games storyboard-ed in house for Android and IOS. Start to finish development including store submissions, in app purchase setup, game center setup. Worked closely with artist to import assets, producers meet expectations and creative to bring the games to life.
- Unity VR Developer Working with various VR headsets and clients to produce unique experiences that exceed expectations and perform in a reliable manor for events, trade shows, public facing as well as internal demos. Clients include Delta Airlines, Charles Schwab Corporation, Georgia Power, InterContinental Hotels Group("IHG"), Nissan Motor Company, College Football Hall of Fame, American Airlines, and Virgin Atlantic
- Unity AR Developer Developed sales tools allowing the user to place and manipulate large equipment in real world space with accurate scale. Created a training tool to assist flight attendants in galley organization in AR and VR. Released an in house production AR app titled "AiR Show" that allows users to place performers in AR space and bring a performance into the users space allowing them to take pictures and videos.

Geek Squad Stockbridge, Georgia

GEEK SQUAD GAME DEVELOPER

May. 2011 - Sept. 2012

- Special project for Geek Squad Academy.
 Game Developer/Programmer creating educational software for Geek Squad Summer Academy.
- Creating the player controls and scripts used to throughout the game.
- Created an avatar editor.

Education

Devry University

Decatur, Georgia

B.S. IN GAME AND SIMULATION PROGRAMMING

Mar. 2007 - Oct. 2010

• Graduated Summa Cum Laude 3.94 / 4.0

September 13, 2021 Travis Gunnyon · Résumé



Tech Experience HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Oculus Quest, Pico VR Headsets, Hololens, Samsung Gear VR,

Various Android/IOS Devices, Google Tango, Structure Sensor, View-Master (2015), Google Cardboard, Rokit Phones

Software Unity, Visual Studio, SureMDM, Photoshop, OBS Studio, GitHub

Project Management Tools Jira, Confluence, Shotgun, Agile Development(Scrum), Basecamp

Programming C-Sharp, JavaScript, C++

Experiments and TestsVuforia, Easy AR plugin, XZIMG plugin, View-Master(2015), multiple AR trackers interacting, Lens Studio for Snapchat, AR

Construction visualization

DevOps AWS, Firebase

Projects

"AiR Show"

- AR music platform for AR capable IOS and Android devices. Display an AR version of the performer that allows you to take photos and videos and bring their performance to life in your living room.
- Developed prototypes for: live-streaming a video hologram in AR, displaying a video hologram in a realtime virtual environment, hologram occlusion on LiDAR capable devices.
- · Acquired by NexTech AR from TRICK 3D

"Delta EX" for Delta Airlines

- Internal platform for Delta Airlines to house multiple VR experience including pano videos and images, virtual tours, vr games, and a custom theater to view standard images and videos.
- · This was used internally and at trade shows supporting several language versions and distributed worldwide internally.

"Skypainter" for Delta Airlines

· Gear VR flying game that transmits an image of the sky you created while playing to a printer and prints out a one of a kind art piece.

"GA Experience" for Georgia Power

• VR camera experience on Android and IOS promoting tourism in Georgia.

Charles Schwab Corporation

• Event display piece for trade shows created for the Pico VR device.

"Armchair Quarterback VR"

• Football experience for Nissan/College Football Hall of Fame displayed at several college football games on the Oculus Rift and connected to D-BOX motion seats.

IHG

• Multiple VR experiences across many of their brands including Holiday Inn, Even Hotels, Atwell Suites, and Avid Hotels. For internal and trade shows. Gear VR and Pico.

American Airlines

• Gear VR plane cabin tour for internal or trade show.

Virgin Atlantic

• Gear VR plane cabin tour for internal or trade show.

HTC VIVE VR Previz Tool

• Vive project that allows you to move around an animated scene in VR and record in game video using real camera like tools and exporting the videos to MP4 for pre-visualization.

"AR/VR Flight Attendant Training Program" for Delta Airlines

• An AR/VR/Ipad app to help flight attendants interacting with the various galley layouts of planes prior to boarding to help familiarize themselves with locations of goods and tools.

Google Tango Project For Delta Airlines

• Cabin visualization in AR space.

Public AR Project for Delta Airlines

• (TBD Covid delayed) QR Code trackers allow users to experience various AR experiences while gaining insight and information on AR capable IOS and Android devices.

"Tool Bucket" for Stanely Black and Decker, Inc.

• Product visualization tool for Ipad that displays various products in app and AR space while providing information and animation.

"Ears the Astronaut"

• 3rd person infinite flying game on IOS and Android.

"Ears- Photobomb"

• AR camera app for IOS.

"Flappy Ears in a Bird Suit: Candy Planet"

• Arcade style platformer for IOS.

"Flappy Easter Egg of Awesomeness"

• Arcade style platformer for IOS.

"Jetpack Kitty Alien Attack"

• Arcade style platformer for IOS.

"Santa's Holiday Gift Grab"

• 1st person race against the clock holiday game.

"Seek 3D - Easter Egg Hunt"

• 1st person race against the clock holiday game.

"Seek 3D - Search for the Golden Egg"

• 1st person race against the clock holiday game.

References

Available Upon Request